

# **ALICIA MORALES**

**COMPUTER SCIENCE FNGINFFR** 

#### ADDRESS:

Hospitalet de Llobregat 08904



### PHONE:

+34 665 37 07 08



### **EMAIL:**

amoralca16@outlook.com



## SKYPE:

alice2360



# **DATE OF BIRTH:**

24 February 1995



### **WEBSITE**:

aliciamorales.ml

# **SKILLS**

**JAVA** 

**PYTHON** 

C

# SOCIAL



facebook.com/aliciamoralescarrasco



twitter.com/amoralca16



linkedin.com/in/aliciamorales-carrasco-81a3ba8

# **PROFESSIONAL PROFILE**

Recent graduate of Computer Science Engineering at Universitat de Barcelona with in-depth knowledge in programming and so much interest in Big Data and Artificial Intelligence. Comprehensive knowledge on database software, experience with Agile methodologies and good oral communication skills in English put the finishing touches on this profile.

"I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work." - Thomas A. Edison

# **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Universitat de Barcelona

MACHINE LEARNING Completed a course on Statistical and Machine Learning where I could learn and practise the fundamentals of ML and Deep Learning with R.

# **GAME DEVELOPER**

2016-2017

Made two game development projects with Unity and C#, one with a team of twenty people and another one in a hackathon. Both were the winners of their respective contests.

## **WEB DEVELOPER**

2016-2017

Created a flight purchasing site using RESTful, Django and Javascript.

# **EDUCATION**

#### **BACHELOR OF COMPUTER** SCIENCE

2013-2018

Universitat de Barcelona

Specialized on Distributed Artificial Intelligence, Distributed Software, Machine Learning and Data Mining. Mark: 8.03

TECH BATXILLERAT Graduated with honors, PAU June 2013. Mark: 9.01

INS Vicenç Plantada

#### **ENGLISH LEVEL**

2014-2015

Escola Oficial d'Idiomes

**B2** Certificate

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **COMPUTER VISION**

02.2018-06.2018 Universitat de Barcelona Developed an image processing and computer vision software for the quantitative analysis of test strips.

# **BIG DATA INTERN**

10 2017-01 2018 Everis Spain, S.L.U.

Supported the development of Big Data projects doing testing, preparing documentation and suggesting improvements. Worked with Big Data Architecture: Spark, Hadoop, Scala, AWS, Azure...

## **TEACHER**

2017-2018 Universitat de Barcelona

Lectured, designed assigments and helped in programming and data structures subjects.